{
	"allQuestions": [{
		"id": 139,
		"question": "Which plant gives us medicines?",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Tulsi", "Castor oil", "Dhatura", "All of these"],
		"correctAnswer": "All of these"
	}, {
		"id": 140,
		"question": "Oil yielding plants are:",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Rice", "Mustard", "Wheat", "Rice"],
		"correctAnswer": "Mustard"
	}, {
		"id": 141,
		"question": "Honey comes from beehives of:",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Butterfly", "Spider", "Honeybee", "None of these"],
		"correctAnswer": "Honeybee"
	}, {
		"id": 142,
		"question": "_____ is extracted by a honey extractor from beehives.",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Honey", "Sugar", "Sarbat", "All of these"],
		"correctAnswer": "Honey"
	}, {
		"id": 143,
		"question": "A small white structure may have grown out of seeds is called:",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Roots", "Stem", "Sprouts", "None of these"],
		"correctAnswer": "sprouts"
	}, {
		"id": 144,
		"question": "Bees collect nectar from:",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Flowers", "Fruits", "Flowers", "None of these"],
		"correctAnswer": "flowers"
	}, {
		"id": 145,
		"question": "Bees store nectar for their use all through the:",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Week", "Year", "Month", "Day"],
		"correctAnswer": "Year"
	}, {
		"id": 146,
		"question": "Eggs are the rich source of:",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Carbohydrates", "Proteins", "Fat", "Oil"],
		"correctAnswer": "Proteins"
	}, {
		"id": 147,
		"question": "Fruits are:",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Tasty", "All of these", "Delicious", "Juicy"],
		"correctAnswer": "all of these"
	}, {
		"id": 148,
		"question": "Honey bee prepare honey in beehives.",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["True", "False"],
		"correctAnswer": "True"
	}, {
		"id": 149,
		"question": "Animals eat both plants and animals.",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["False", "True"],
		"correctAnswer": "True"
	}, {
		"id": 150,
		"question": "Fish are major sources of proteins.",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["True", "False"],
		"correctAnswer": "True"
	}, {
		"id": 151,
		"question": "Food helps in body buildings.",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["True", "False"],
		"correctAnswer": "True"
	}, {
		"id": 152,
		"question": "Those animals that eating other animals are called:",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Carnivores", "Omnivores", "Herbivores", "None of these"],
		"correctAnswer": "Carnivores"
	}, {
		"id": 153,
		"question": "_____ is the ability to do work.",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Strength", "Hard work", "Energy", "None of these"],
		"correctAnswer": "Energy"
	}, {
		"id": 154,
		"question": "Animals which not give us milk",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Tiger", "Cows", "Camel", "Goat"],
		"correctAnswer": "Tiger"
	}, {
		"id": 155,
		"question": "Which part of the Brinjal plant we generally eat ?",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Fruit", "Branches", "Root", "Seeds"],
		"correctAnswer": "fruit"
	}, {
		"id": 156,
		"question": "Which part of sugarcane we generally eat?",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Root", "Stem/Branch", "Leaves", "Seeds"],
		"correctAnswer": "Stem/Branch"
	}, {
		"id": 157,
		"question": "Plants gives us more varieties of:",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Milk", "Gas", "Food", "Curd"],
		"correctAnswer": "Food"
	}, {
		"id": 158,
		"question": "Sugar is obtained from the leaves of sugarcane.",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["True", "False"],
		"correctAnswer": "False"
	}, {
		"id": 159,
		"question": "Tiger is a Omnivores.",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["False", "True"],
		"correctAnswer": "False"
	}, {
		"id": 160,
		"question": "An oily thin paper sheet will be:",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Translucent", "Transparent", "Opaque", "Cannot be predicted"],
		"correctAnswer": "translucent"
	}, {
		"id": 161,
		"question": "Which is a set of transparent materials?",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Glass and air", "Water and glass", "Water and air", "All of these"],
		"correctAnswer": "All of these"
	}, {
		"id": 162,
		"question": "Choose the opaque object from the following:",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Water", "Charcoal", "Glass", "Air"],
		"correctAnswer": "Charcoal"
	}, {
		"id": 163,
		"question": "Which object shines?",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Cotton shirt", "Steel spoon", "Plastic toy", "Stone piece"],
		"correctAnswer": "Steel spoon"
	}, {
		"id": 164,
		"question": "Which of the following has reddish brown colour?",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Iron", "Gold", "Copper", "Silver"],
		"correctAnswer": "Iron"
	}, {
		"id": 165,
		"question": "Which one of the following is insoluble in water?",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["Milk", "Alcohol", "Sugar", "Oil"],
		"correctAnswer": "Oil"
	}, {
		"id": 166,
		"question": "The amount of matter in any object is called its weight.",
		"category": "science",
		"answer": ["False", "True"],
		"correctAnswer": "False"
	}]
}
